-=旧域名被黑 启用新网址=-
-=梦幻天堂·龙网=-
http://www.lwgod.com
(1959年麻州 列克星顿)
Lucinda, we're going in.
卢辛达 我们要进去了
Lucinda!
卢辛达
Lucinda, we're going in.
卢辛达 我们该进去了
Lucinda!
卢辛达
Now, you remember tomorrow is our official opening day, don't you?
还记得吗 明天是我们正式建校的日子
- Yes, Miss Taylor. - Yes, Miss Taylor.
- 记得 泰勒老师 - 记得 泰勒老师
And you remember Principal Clark ran a competition last month
还记得上个月克拉克校长组织的竞赛吗
to find the best ideas to celebrate this very special day.
要找出最好的方式来欢庆这特殊的日子
- Me! Me! Me! - Me! Me! Me!
- 是我 - 我 我 我 我 我
Well, yesterday, the staff selected the winning idea,
昨天工作人员挑出了最好的方法
and it came from this class.
而且这个主意出自我们班
The winner is our own
获胜者是我们的
Lucinda Embry.
卢辛达·恩布里
- Lucinda? - Why her?
- 卢辛达？- 为什么是她
- Lucinda? - Lucinda?
- 卢辛达？- 卢辛达？
Come on, everyone.
大家快鼓掌啊
We'll be closing our dedication ceremony with the burial of a time capsule.
我们将以地下封存时光胶囊来结束 我们的开学典礼
- Yes? - What's a time capsule?
- 什么事 - 什么是时光胶囊
This is a time capsule.
这就是个时光胶囊
- Wow. - That's incredible.
- 哇 - 难以置信
Now, I need you to put your thinking caps on,
现在大家把思考的帽子戴上
because I want each of you to draw
因为我想让大家画一张画
what you think the future is going to look like.
画出你认为的未来的样子
Then we'll put the pictures in the capsule, and 50 years from today,
然后我们会把图画放到时光胶囊里 50年后的今天
a group of children just like yourselves will open it up to see what you drew.
一群和你们一样大的孩子 会打开看你们画的什么
Doesn't that sound exciting?
是不是很激动人心啊
- Yes, Miss Taylor. - Yes, Miss Taylor.
- 是的 泰勒老师 - 是的 泰勒老师
Let's begin.
那我们开始吧
That is a lovely spaceship there, Dawn.
多恩 你画的宇宙飞船真漂亮
- Thank you, Miss Taylor. - Well done.
- 谢谢 泰勒老师 - 真不错
And that is a nice robot, Andrew. Very good.
安德鲁这个机器人也画得很好 非常棒
Time's up. Everyone hand your work in.
时间到 所有人都交上来
And make sure you write your name on the envelope.
记住把自己的名字写在信封上
My name's over here.
我的名字在这
- Thank you, Harold. - Thank you, Miss Taylor.
- 谢谢 霍里德 - 谢谢 泰勒老师
Lucinda, you need to finish up now.
卢辛达 你得抓紧时间画完
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- 谢谢 - 谢谢
Oh, Lucinda.
卢辛达
The assignment was to draw a picture.
要求是画一幅画
This was your idea.
这还是你的主意呢
Okay, I want you all to finish, please.
好了 请大家都交上来
Welcome to all our friends and esteemed colleagues.
欢迎各位朋友和尊贵的同仁们
We, the students and faculty of William Dawes Elementary,
我们威廉·道斯小学的全体师生
hereby bury this time capsule in dedication of our new school,
在此要以埋藏时光胶囊 献给我们的建校典礼
and we charge our descendents
我们会让我们的后代在50年后的今天
to open this vault of history 50 years from today.
打开具有历史意义的地下室
To the future and the promise that it holds.
献给它所承载的未来
(时空胶囊)
Lucinda?
卢辛达？
I'm certain Lucinda is simply being over curious.
我敢说卢辛达只是好奇心太重了
Can you please help find her?
拜托你一定找到她
The cloakroom. Check the cloakroom.
衣帽间 查看一下衣帽间
Lucinda. Henry, come on.
卢辛达·亨利 快点
- Lucinda? - Come on out now.
- 卢辛达？- 快点出来吧
Lucinda?
卢辛达？
Lucinda.
卢辛达
Oh, my God.
上帝啊
Make them stop. Please make them stop whispering.
让他们停下来 不要再说耳语了
(现在)
Caleb? Take a look at this.
凯莱布 过来看一下
There you go.
进去吧
What is it?
什么东西
Saturn's rings await your approval.
土星的光环等着你去证明呢
Has anyone found life on other planets?
有没有人在其他星球上发现生命存在
Not yet. Guess it's just us for now.
还没有 我猜现在只有我们人类
Okay. Then how many that might have life?
那有多少可能会存在生命呢
Well, if you count the number of stars similar to our sun in this galaxy,then you
如果你计算像太阳这样 有像地球一样的行星
factor in the probability that they have Earth-like planets orbiting them
绕其公转的恒星的话 在银河系的数字可能是
There are 10 million possible worlds
会有1000万个世界
with four million mature enough for life to evolve.
其中四百万个成熟到有生命进化
Why do you even ask?
那你还问什么
Just making sure if you're listening.
只是想看一下你是不是在听
- Where you going? - To watch that Discovery program.
- 你去哪 - 去看探索频道
But it's Dad's famous Sunday night hot dogs on the run...
这可是老爸最拿手的热狗
...time.
每周日晚上的
I can't consume that. I've decided to become a vegetarian.
我不能吃了 我决定吃素
Well, when were you planning on telling the guy
那你什么时候告诉
who buys the groceries around here?
负责采购的人呢
Are you deaf? I just told you now, Dad.
你聋了吗 我刚刚告诉你了 爸爸
The cubs are now six months old and bounding with energy,
小老虎只有六个月大 精力充沛
but, any parent knows, this is also a mixed blessing.
但是 所有的父母都知道 这也不是太好
- Off. - No, it's almost over.
- 关了 - 不 马上就结束了
You're not gonna be able to concentrate in class tomorrow.
明天你就不能在课堂上集中精力听讲了
I don't have class tomorrow. It's the 50th anniversary, remember?
明天没有课 是50年校庆 不记得了吗
I remember.
记得
Caleb,
凯莱布
when I said it was just us out there,
当我在外面说只有我们存在的时候
you know I was talking about space, right?
你知道我指的是太空吧
I didn't mean heaven, or anything.
我没有说天堂 或其他的
- I'm sure wherever Mom is... - Dad, you don't even believe in heaven.
无论妈妈在哪 - 爸爸 你都不相信有天堂
I never said that, Caleb.
我没这么说过 凯莱布
I just said we can't know for sure, that's all.
我只是说我们不知道 就这个意思
If you want to believe, you go ahead and believe, okay?
如果你想相信的话 你信就是了 好吗
Okay. Bedtime.
好了 该睡觉了
Hey, you and me,
你和我
- together forever. - Forever.
- 永远在一起 - 永远
I love you.
我爱你
I love you, too.
我也爱你
(麻省理工学院)
We're going to pose a topic
我们要提出一个话题
to get you thinking along the right lines for your term paper.
让大家在学期报告中不会跑题
It's the subject of randomness versus determinism in the universe.
话题是宇宙中随机论与决对论的对决
Who's jumping in? Jessica?
投给谁呢 杰西卡
Determinism says that occurrences in nature
决对论称自然界的一切
are causally decided by preceding events or natural laws,
是由可预知的事情或自然规律事先决定好的
that everything leading up to this point has happened for a reason.
所有一切的发生都是有原因的
That's right. That's what determinism says.
很好 决定论就是这样的
Spencer? Tell me something about the sun.
斯宾塞 告诉我关于太阳的知识
It's hot.
它很热
Elaborate.
说详细点
Temperature's about 10,000 degrees Fahrenheit on the surface,
表层温度大约是10 000华氏度
- 27 million degrees at the core. - Good.
- 核心部位是2700万华氏度 - 很好
Stacey?
史黛丝？
A word or two about the composition.
用一两个词说一下它的构成
Mostly hydrogen.
大部分是氢
Also helium with some carbon and nitrogen thrown in there.
其中还有氦 碳和氮
Excellent. Now, I want you to think about the perfect set of circumstances
非常好 现在我要你们开始考虑完美的距离
that put this celestial ball of fire
这个天空中的火球
at just the correct distance
距离我们生命得以延续的蓝色地球
from our little blue planet for life to evolve,
正好的距离
making it possible for you to be sitting here in this riveting lecture.
这样才让你们有机会坐在这里 听到如此精彩的演讲
But that's a nice thought, right?
但这是一个不错的想法 对吗
Everything has a purpose, an order to it, is determined.
每一件事都是有目的的 有规律的 是决定好的
But then there's the other side of the argument,
但之后还有另一种论证
the theory of randomness, which says it's all simply coincidence.
就是随机理论 认为所有的事情都是简单的偶然事件
The very fact we exist is nothing but the result of a complex
我们的存在就是许多事情的结果
yet inevitable string of chemical accidents
不可避免的一系列的化学反应
and biological mutations.
和生物的变异
There is no grand meaning.
没有什么深刻意义
There's no purpose.
没有目的
What about you, Professor Koestler?
那你呢 凯斯特勒教授
- What? - Well, what do you believe?
- 什么 - 你相信什么呢
I think shit just happens.
我认为这一切就这么发生了
But that's me. Class dismissed.
只是我个人观点 下课
Now, that's some very heavy shit for a Monday morning, by the sounds of it.
听起来周一早上讲这些 有点沉重了吧
Since when does the cosmology department audit my lectures?
什么时候宇宙学系也来审查我的课了
Since my esteemed colleague in astrophysics owes me a latte.
自从受人尊敬天体物理学同事欠我一杯拿铁咖啡
So what's on your scientific mind today?
那么你今天有什么科学见解
Do you remember Kim's little sister? Ph-double D's? Remember her?
还记得金姆的小妹吗 双博士学位 记得吗
Is it ethical to say things like that about your sister- in- law?
伦理学上就是说你的小姨子
What? It's factual. It's peer-reviewed. I mean, it's like...,
怎么了 实际上就是 我们也是同行 我是说 就是…
Anyway whatever.
没什么 不管怎样
- She's in town this Friday. - Okay.
- 她周五要来镇上 - 好啊
And she thinks that you're intriguing, which I thought was code for gay,
她觉得你很有魅力 我先前以为她是指你对同性恋很冷淡
but apparently not because she's asked if you would join us for dinner.
但显然不是 她想邀请你一起共进晚餐
- Yeah, I... I don't know, Phil. - Come on, John.
- 是吗我不知道 菲尔 - 别这样 约翰
Come on, you owe me for last time you skipped out on me.
去吧 你上次溜走还欠我个人情
- Caleb was panicking. - Yeah, look, I know.
- 凯莱布很惊慌 - 是啊 我知道
And the time before that, he had a sore throat.
再上一次他是嗓子疼
- Oh, no. - What?
- 坏了 - 怎么了
- Damn it! Damn it! - What?
- 坏了 该死 - 怎么了
Caleb's ceremony. I'm sorry, Phil.
凯莱布的典礼 对不起 菲尔
Hey! Hey! Friday!
记住 周五
I'll think about it!
我会考虑的
#- This little light of mine - This little light of mine#
#- 我的这把小火炬 - 我的这把小火炬#
#- I'm gonna let it shine - I'm gonna let it shine#
#- 我要让它闪闪亮 - 我要让它闪闪亮#
#- This little light of mine - This little light of mine#
(威廉·道斯小学50周年校庆)
#- 我的这把小火炬 - 我的这把小火炬#
#- I'm gonna let it shine - I'm gonna let it shine#
#- 我要让它闪闪亮 - 我要让它闪闪亮#
#- This little light of mine - This little light of mine#
#- 我的这把小火炬 - 我的这把小火炬#
#- I'm gonna let it shine - I'm gonna let it shine#
#- 我要让它闪闪亮 - 我要让它闪闪亮#
#Let it shine, let it shine, let it shine#
#让它闪 让它闪 让它闪#
Fifty years ago, the students and faculty of William Dawes Elementary
50年前威廉·道斯小学的全体师生
imagined what the future might hold. Today, we unveil their legacy.
想象未来会是什么样的 现在我们要揭开留给我们赠物
Now, I'd like to introduce you to someone very special,
现在我要向大家介绍特殊嘉宾
Miss Priscilla Taylor.
泰勒老师
Since Miss Taylor was there for the original dedication,
因为泰勒老师当时参加了最初的建校典礼
it's only fitting that we have her do the honors today.
今天由她来剪彩是最合适的人选
(时空胶囊)
WOW!
哇噢
You almost forgot again.
你差点又忘记了
I made it in time to hear you sing. You were the best one up there.
我还是赶到听你唱歌了 你是台上最棒的
- You could not hear me. - I could. I swear.
- 你听不见我唱 - 我听得见 我发誓
Gotta go. They're starting!
该走了 要开始了
All right, easy, easy! No pushing.
好了 不要急 不要急 不要推
Everyone is going to receive an envelope.
每个人都会收到一封信的
Open them gently now. They're very old.
慢慢的打开 它们很旧了
Miss Taylor! Miss Taylor!
泰勒老师 泰勒老师
Thank you.
谢谢
Everyone's gonna get one.
每个人都会得到一个的
- Hello again, John. - Hello. How's it going?
- 你好约翰 又见面了 - 你好 还好吗
(卢辛达·恩布里)
Hey, What'd you get?
你的是什么
Boring. Everyone else got a picture.
无聊 其他人都收到图画了
Caleb, could you please watch where you put this?
凯莱布 你能不能小心点把它放好
I don't want you to lose another one.
我不想让你再丢一个
It's making funny noises.
总是有奇怪的声音
Try turning the volume down.
把声音关小点
Hey, Dad? You know that kid, Jason, from soccer practice?
爸爸 你还记得那个在足球队的男孩杰森吗
Mmm-hmm.
记得
He's having a sleepover this weekend, and he was wondering if I can come.
他周末要举行狂欢夜 问我是否能去参加
Sounds like fun.
听起来很有趣
They have a boat.
他们还有艘船
Jason's dad said he might take us out on the lake.
杰森的爸爸说他可以带我们去湖上玩
I'll think about it.
我会考虑的
- That means no. - It means I'll think about it.
- 那就是不行了 - 意思是我会考虑的
What are you doing with this?
你拿这个做什么
You weren't supposed to bring this home. It belongs to the school.
你不应该带回家 这是学校的东西
But maybe it means something, like a math puzzle or something like that.
也许它有什么含义 比如数学谜题什么的
Yeah, that's good, I don't know, but it's not ours to keep.
是啊 想法不错 我不知道 但不应该拿回家
Now, you return this as soon as you get to school tomorrow. Got it?
明天一到学校就尽快还回去
Okay, let's go. Bedtime.
好了 睡觉时间到了
#O'er thy spirit gently stealing#
#你在我整个夜晚#
#I my loving vigil keeping#
#爱的守护中#
#All through the night#
#慢慢睡去#
Goodnight, baby.
晚安 宝贝
Goodnight, Mom.
晚安 妈妈
(儿童频道节目表)
Our tigress lives in Kanha National Park,
这些老虎居住在卡妮娜国家公园
in the forests of Kipling's Jungle Book,
在季普林热带丛林里面
where dawn elephant patrols
那里早上会有大象巡逻
ensure this is one of the safest places for tigers to roam.
确保此地是最安全的地方
Year after year...
年复一年
Damn it.
该死
9/11/01.
9/11/01
(为了纪念那天失去的2996条生命)
Two thousand, nine hundred and ninety-six.
两千九百九十六
Come on.
不会吧
What the hell is this?
这到底是什么东西
(墨西哥市死了10153人)
(4056人死亡)
(巨无霸客机坠毁270死)
(奥克拉荷马市爆炸168死)
In the aftermath of Hurricane Katrina...
在卡特里娜飓风过后
There could be thousands of bodies here...
可能会有无数的尸体
Oh, my God.
上帝啊
Dad?
爸爸？
Dad, we're gonna be late!
爸爸 我们要晚了
Do you have your knapsack all set?
包里的东西都装好了吗
Thanks for the ride, Mr.Koestler.
谢谢你载我们 凯斯特勒先生
Dad, are you sick?
爸爸 你生病了吗
I'm fine.
我没事
Don't you think you're acting kind of awkward today?
你不觉得你今天行动比较迟钝吗
Am I awkward? I just had a lot of work to do last night.
我迟钝？只是昨晚工作太多了
Okay.
好吧
- Bye, Dad. - Bye.
- 再见 爸爸 - 再见
(麻省理工学院观测站)
(麻省威斯福特镇)
Look at this.
看看这个
- Look at the numbers beside the date. - Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
- 看看日期旁边的数字 - 是 看到了
Two thousand, nine hundred and ninety-six.
两千九百九十六
Right.
对
That's how many people died in the attacks that day.
那就是在袭击当天死亡人数
- Yeah. - All right, stay with me.
- 是的 - 好了 听我讲
I know how this sounds, but I've matched these numbers to the dates
我知道这听起来很怪 但是我已经核对了过去50年里
of every major global disaster for the last 50 years in perfect sequence,
全球所有的灾难的死亡数字和日期 并且完全正确
except for three.
除了这三个
And these events haven't occurred yet, starting with this one.
这些事件还没有发生 从这个开始
So tomorrow, somewhere on the planet, this number string predicts
所以明天 地球某个地方 这个数字就会出现
that 81 people are gonna die in some kind of tragedy.
81个人将死于某种悲惨的事件
- Whoa. I mean, have a listen to yourself. - I know.
- 哇 我的意思是 听听你说的 - 我知道
- It sounds pretty crazy. - I know.
- 听起来很疯狂 - 我知道
I mean, even for you.
我是说 连你也会相信
- What's this? - Open it.
- 什么东西 - 打开看一下
(饭店大火48死)
Oh!
噢
Why are you showing me this?
你为什么给我看这个
The day Allison died in the fire, it's on the list, too,
艾利森死于火中的日期也在数字单里
from a piece of paper that's been buried in the ground for five decades.
在地下埋了50年的一张纸里
- Yeah. - Can you explain that, Phil?
- 是吗 - 你能给我解释一下吗 菲尔
I was up all night going over this. I went through that list again and again,
我一夜没睡来整理这个 一遍又一遍的核对这张数字单
and I tried to fault it and I couldn't.
我试图否定它 但是我做不到
Maybe someone's playing a really shitty joke...
也许某个人正在跟你开低级玩笑
Right! Right! Except I saw them dig it up!
是啊 是啊 但是我看见他们挖出来的
I watched them pull the capsule out of the ground
我看见他们把容器从地下取出
and hand that sealed envelope to my kid.
把那个密封的信封给了我的孩子
Okay, let me ask you this, then.
好吧 我来问问这个
All these uncircled numbers, what do they mean?
这些不画圈的数字有什么意思
I don't know yet. Maybe nothing. But the circled...
我不知道 也许没有意义 但是画圈的…
Maybe they all mean nothing.
也许他们都没有意义
Okay, Phil, hey, can we just start over here?
好吧 菲尔 我们能不能从这里开始
I'm not saying that 81 people are going to die tomorrow, okay?
我没有说81个人明天就会死 好吗
I'm just trying to understand why this is saying they will.
我只是想知道为什么它说将会发生
Okay, it's spooky, all right? I'll grant you. It's more than spooky.
好吧 这很可怕 好吗 我承认这不仅可怕
But just step back, all right?
但是不要再研究了 好吗
You have all these uncircled numbers with no sequence to them.
这些没有画圈的数字都没有意义
I mean, numerology, kabala, Pythagorean cults,
我是说数字占卜术 犹太神秘哲学 毕达哥拉斯神学
there are systems that find meaning in numbers,
我们有很多系统可以发现数字的含义
and they are a dime a dozen. Why?
而且多的不稀罕 为什么呢
Because people see what they want to see in them.
因为人们只愿意领会他们想要的
I mean, that's really what you think I'm doing?
那你就是这么认为我现在做的一切吗
Yeah, I think that losing Allison has spun you off your axis a little,
是的 我觉得失去艾利森有点让你失去信仰
and I think it's clouded your judgment.
我觉得这影响了你的判断力
I'm just saying it's clouded your judgment.
我说影响了你的判断力
Don't you think?
你不这样认为吗
- Where are you going? - Off campus.
- 你去哪 - 离开
(分机故障)
Yes?
有什么事
But you do remember her?
你还记得她对吗
Oh, yes. I remember Lucinda.
是的 我记得卢辛达
She was such a sad little girl.
它是一个闷闷不乐的女孩
Would you like some iced tea?
你想喝点冰茶吗
Oh, no. Thank you. Thank you.
不 不用了 谢谢
Do you remember the day your students buried the time capsule?
你还记得你的学生埋藏时光胶囊的那天吗
Oh, yes. The children were so excited.
记得 孩子们都很兴奋
And what about Lucinda?
卢辛达兴奋吗
That was the day we couldn't find her.
那天我们都找不到她
She was hiding in a closet, under the gym,
她藏到体育馆下面的衣橱里面
scratching at the door with her fingernails like some kind of animal.
用手指甲抓挠橱门 像某种动物似的
Scratching at the door?
抓挠橱门？
- Why was she hiding? - I'm not sure.
- 她为什么要躲起来 - 我不知道
She was holding up the class writing all those silly numbers.
她整堂课都在写那些莫名的数字
I had to hurry her along.
我不得不催她赶快交
Then we found her,
之后我们找到了她
and I knew something had frightened the poor dear,
我只知道她肯定是受到了惊吓
but we never could get her to tell us what it was.
但她却不肯说到底受是什么
Miss Taylor, my son got Lucinda's time capsule message.
泰勒小姐 我儿子拿到了卢辛达藏在时光胶囊里的信
Do you remember this? Is this what she wrote?
你还记得这个吗 这是她写的吗
Oh, Professor, you are testing an old woman's memory.
教授 你这是在考验一个老女人的记忆
- Can you believe it's been 50 years? - It's a long time.
- 你能相信吗 已经过了50年了 - 是很久了
I believe that's it.
我觉得这正是她写的
How rude of me.
看我多无礼
I never offered you a drink. Would you like some iced tea?
我都没给你喝的东西 冰茶好吗
No, thank you. I'm fine.
不用了 谢谢 我不渴
I thought maybe I could meet her.
我想我能不能和她见一面
Oh! I'm sorry. Lucinda passed away several years ago.
真遗憾 卢辛达几年前就过世了
I said I'm Caleb Koestler's father.
我是凯莱布·凯斯特勒的父亲
I'm calling to find out the names of the two janitors
我想问一下昨天仪式上打开时光胶囊的
that pulled the time capsule out of the ground yesterday at the ceremony.
两位校职工的姓名
I'm not sure I understand why that would be a problem for you.
我不明白为什么在你看来这成问题
Yes, sir, we're afraid that that's privileged information.
先生 这些属于内部资料
Caleb!
凯莱布
- Who was that? - I don't know. Just some guys.
- 那是谁 - 不知道 过路人吧
What did he give you?
他给了你什么
Just this. Kind of cool, isn't it?
就这个 很酷吧 不是吗
What did I say about talking to strangers?
你忘了我说过不要和陌生人说话吗
Have you done your homework?
功课做完了吗
Give me 10 more minutes of practice.
再让我多练10分钟吧
I don't want to have to ask you twice, Caleb. Come on.
我不想说第二遍 凯莱布 快去
(卢辛达·恩布里死亡)
(本地妇女尸体被人发现)
Hey!
嘿
Hey, stranger.
嘿 陌生人
At what age do we learn to knock?
你几岁才能学会敲门
I said I was going to drop by on my way to the graveyard shift, remember?
我说了会顺路来看你 然后去墓地换班 记得吗
- Didn't you get my message? - I've been busy.
- 你没收到我消息吗 - 我一直很忙
Can you not play with my things?
你可以不要碰我的东西吗
- You're always busy. - Yes! Yes.
- 你总是很忙 - 是的 是的
- How's my nephew? - Decided to become a vegetarian.
- 我外甥怎样 - 他决定做素食主义者
- A what? - Why, you got a problem with that?
- 什么 - 怎么 你有意见吗
You're not feeding him Dad's famous Sunday night hot dogs again, are you?
你没再给他吃著名的爸爸周日晚热狗了吧
You know, if you want someone to take him off your hands for the evening
如果你想在晚上找人照看他
so you can go out, you know, like normal people do...
你能像其他人一样晚上出去找点乐子
I appreciate the offer, but we're fine.
非常感谢 但是我们不需要
And, believe it or not, Caleb and I have got a good thing going here.
还有 信不信随你 凯莱布和我互动很好
Uh-huh?
是吗
Yeah. So you can report that back to headquarters.
是的 你可以把这个汇报给总部
Mom says hi. So does Dad.
爸妈要我问候你
Grace, don't.
格莱斯 不要这样
I get that you don't like being the son of a pastor.
我理解你不想做一个牧师的孩子
I am the son of a pastor.
我是牧师的孩子
That's fine.
那没什么
- You're still his son. Can't you let it go? - Can't he?
- 你始终是他儿子 你就不能算了吗 - 他能吗
You know he asks after you every time I see him.
我每次见到他 他都会问你的情况
- He worries about you. - He said that?
- 他很牵挂你 - 他亲口说的吗
- He doesn't have to. - Right.
- 他不用说出口 - 是啊
You're going to have to speak to him one day, you know.
总有一天你要和他说话的
This can't go on forever.
不可能一直这样下去
You know it's what Allison wanted,
你也知道这是艾利森的心愿
for Caleb to have a grandfather, and vice versa.
让他们祖孙团圆
Okay, I'm going. I'm going.
好吧 我走了 我走了
By the way, Grace, how are you? How's your life? What's going on for you?
顺便问一句 格莱斯 你好吗 你过得如何 发生了什么
- Thank you, John, for asking. - I have to get up early in the morning.
- 谢谢关心 约翰 - 我早上要早起
What have you got going on? I'll say a prayer.
你到底怎么了 我可以为你祷告
Please...
别…
Don't.
别这样
Okay.
好吧
And at the ASX 200 index in Australia,
今天的澳大利亚ASX200指数
one of the bigger losers today so far in the recession,
是自从经济衰退以来的最大跌幅
down about 1.5%...
下跌约1.5个百分点
The dispute has now lasted for some three weeks,
争论已经持续了约3周
with talks yet to resolve the issue.
仍未解决的问题
Experts say solar flares this weekend may disrupt cell phone communication...
本周专家声称太阳耀斑可能干扰手机信号
- Experts. -... and some satellite transmissions.
- 专家 - 以及一些卫星通讯
The problems can...
这个问题…
The attorney for the family talked to reporters
家庭律师告诉记者
after the press conference today.
今天的新闻发布会后
The price of oil hit yet another record.
油价再创新高
A devastating fire burns out of control in the Gulf.
一场毁灭性的大火在海湾燃烧
That story leads our headlines at the top of the hour.
这个故事是我们的头条新闻
Plus, all the latest world news at midnight on October 15th.
还有 所有十月十五日晚间最新的新闻
Eighty-one.
Tonight, in the Gulf of Mexico,
今晚 在墨西哥湾
an explosion on a soon-to-be decommissioned oilrig
一个即将停止使用的油井发生爆炸
triggered a fire which burned for three hours before it was extinguished.
大火足足烧了3个小时才被熄灭
Officials don't yet know the exact cause of the explosion,
有关方面还未得知爆炸的原因
but believe a malfunction in the cooling system may have been at fault.
但有消息称是冷却系统发生故障造成的
Our last run into the rig
我们最后一次使用油井
Due to the prompt response of the rescue unit,
由于救援队的及时反应
the structure was evacuated with no loss of life.
人员都被疏散 没有人员伤亡
Farmers across the Midwest
中西部的农民
are continuing to feel the effects of a record drought...
正遭遇创纪录的干旱
Across China and Southeast Asia
在中国和东南亚
And here's Carl with the weather.
- 这里是卡尔主持的天气预报
- Looks like a scorcher's on the way. - That's right, Bob.
- 看来热浪正在逼近 - 你说的对 鲍勃
The forecast shows more high pressure moving in later this week.
天气预报显示更多高气压在本周后期到达
It seems our Indian summer is set to last a little while longer,
看来我们的印度夏天会延长了
so don't put away your hats and your sunscreen just yet.
所以别急着脱帽子 防晒要做好
Temperatures are set to reach another record high this week.
本周气温将会再创新高
Thunderstorms are blowing across...
暴风雨正席卷
- Hello? - Dad, where are you?
- 你好 - 爸爸 你在哪里
You're on carpool this afternoon.
你下午得来汽车站
Caleb, I am so sorry.
凯莱布 我很抱歉
I'll pick you up in 10 minutes. Okay?
我十分钟后来接你 好吗
Okay. Bye.
好的 再见
William Dawes Elementary School, alternate route.
威廉·道斯小学 其他路径
No alternate route available.
没有其他路径
Hey, you've dialed Phil and Kim.
你好 你之前找过菲尔和金姆
We can't get to the phone right now, so please leave a message.
我们现在不能接听你的电话
Hey, Phil, it's John.
嘿 菲尔 我是约翰
I'm sorry about yesterday.
昨天真不好意思
I kind of freaked out on you, didn't I?
我昨天有点失态了
Well, look, I'm not ready to meet anyone in any kind of special way, you know,
听着 我还没准备好和谁深入接触 你知道的
but I would like to take you up on your offer for dinner.
但我想接受你的邀请共进晚餐
I think it would be good for me to just, you know, get out of the house and...
我想这应该对我有好处 离开家里 出来走走
(现在位置)
The uncircled numbers are locations.
没有画圈的数字是坐标
This location.
这个地点
Get back in your vehicles. We'll clear this up in a minute.
回车上去 我们马上清理干净
Get these people back in their cars!
让这些人回车上去
We can open up the far lane.
我们可以开通那条车道
What's going on? Can we get through or what?
怎么回事 我们能通过吗
Hi. ls everything okay?
一切还好吧
I'm sorry, sir, but you need to get back to your car.
抱歉 先生 请你回到车上去
- Anybody hurt? - A couple of injuries, but nothing serious.
- 有人受伤吗 - 有人受伤了 但不严重
Get down! Get away!
趴下 快跑
Hey! Hey!
嘿 嘿
Help me! Please!
请你救救我
Help me!
救救我
Help me, please! Help me!
救我
Are you okay, sir?
你还好吗 先生
Step back, sir. Step away.
退后 先生 离开这里
Today we witnessed one of the worst days in recent US aviation history
今天我们经历了美国航空历史最悲惨的一天
when four planes crash-landed across as many states from Maine to Miami.
四架飞机实施了紧急降落
One tragically ended in disaster when Flight 74 from Pittsburgh came down
但一架从匹兹堡起飞的74航班
2 miles from the runway near Logan International Airport and exploded...
在离洛根国际机场跑道还有两公里的地方爆炸了
Can you go upstairs while I talk to your dad?
你上楼去吧 我要跟你爸爸谈话
No act of terrorism is expected to be involved.
排除恐怖主义
The National Transportation Safety Board is looking into possibilities
国家运输安全委员会正在展开调查
that a malfunction in the navigational systems of the planes caused the crashes...
可能由于导航系统故障导致飞机坠毁
- You didn't tell him anything? - Of course not.
- 你没告诉他吧 - 当然没有
First estimates put the presumed dead at 81.
初步估计81人遇难
- Do you need to talk? - NTS is Linking
- 你想谈谈吗 - NTS正在连线
possible navigational malfunctions
可能是导航仪的故障
- to an unprecedented level... - I just...
- 到达了一个前所未有的水平 - 我只是
...of electromagnetic radiation from a series...
电磁辐射
I just want to sleep.
我只想睡觉
Government officials are quick to reiterate that at this time
政府方面马上再次重申
no act of terrorism is suspected to be involved.
不是恐怖主义所为
What happened, Dad? What's going on?
发生什么了 爸爸
Truck broke down on the highway.
高速上的卡车出故障了
It's more than that, isn't it?
不止这些 对吗
I'm going to bed.
我要上床了
Get your homework done.
你把作业做好
And you should go to bed, too. No TV tonight.
然后也该上床了 今晚不准看电视
- Why? I always watch an hour of TV. - No more questions, Caleb.
- 为什么 我平时都看1小时电视 - 不要再问了 凯莱布
I can ask questions when you tell me things to do that don't make sense.
你让我做说不通的事情时 我可以提问
You won't let me play soccer, you won't let me stay over at Jason's,
你不让我踢球 不让我在杰森家过夜
and now you won't tell me what's going on
现在又不告诉我到底发生什么
and why you're acting so weird all the time.
也不告诉我为什么你今天这么奇怪
I'm not a kid anymore.
我已经长大了
(列克星顿空难81人罹难)
Oh, my God. John, you... You were there?
天哪 约翰 你当时在现场吗
The date, the number of dead, the GPS coordinates, lat and long.
日期 遇难人数 GPS坐标 经度和纬度
- Why didn't I see that? - It wasn't coincidence.
- 为什么我没发现 - 那不是巧合
I drove past at the exact moment the prediction came true.
事故发生的时间我正好路过那
It's not coincidence.
这不是巧合
Okay, John, I didn't say it was.
好吧 约翰 我没说这是巧合
So what are we calling this? Synchronicity?
那这是什么 同步性吗
Two unrelated events, digging up a time capsule, plane crash,
两个毫不相干的事件 挖出时光胶囊 飞机坠毁
combined to create a significance for the subject, you?
得出一个重大的结论 你吗
I keep seeing their faces,
那些脸一直在我脑海闪现
burning.
燃烧着
Oh, man.
天哪
Okay, look. We're way beyond the bounds here, John.
听着 这已经超出我们的能力了 约翰
We don't have a frame of reference.
我们没有参照标准
There could be multiple meanings to consider.
可能有其他意义
There are two disasters left.
还有两个灾难
What are you saying?
你在说什么
The numbers are warnings meant for me.
这些数字对我来说是种警示
They might just as easily be a warning to stay away.
它可能只是警示你让你远离
You could have been killed today, John. Caleb would have been orphaned,
你今天差点没命 约翰 凯莱布差点变成孤儿
and you want to go put yourself back in harm's way?
你还想让自己陷入危险吗
Two disasters left.
还有两件事故会发生
Right now my scientific mind is telling me to have nothing more to do with this,
现在我科学家的头脑告诉我 这跟我无关
and yours should, too.
你也一样
Dad!
爸爸
Caleb, what's wrong? What's wrong?
凯莱布 怎么了 发生什么了
Dad!
爸爸
It's okay. It's okay.
没事了 没事了
It's just a bad dream.
只是噩梦
只是噩梦罢了
Hey!
嘿
站住
You stay away from us, you hear?
给我滚远一点 听到没有
Want some of this?
想尝尝我的厉害吗
One, two, three...
(本地妇女尸体被人发现)
1 2 3…
(露辛妲安布里 韦伦)
- Got your hat, honey? - Yeah.
- 拿好帽子 - 好
Caleb, why don't you check out the dire wolf?
凯莱布 去看看恶狼吧
- I'll catch up with you, okay? - Okay.
- 我过会来接你 - 好
Do you know that all wolves are born deaf?
你知道吗 狼出生就是聋的
Really?
真的吗
But, you know, when they get older,
但是当它们长大后
they can hear another wolf's howl from 10 miles away.
他们在10英里外就能听到同伴的嚎叫
Wow. How did you know that?
你怎么知道的
I read it in a National Geographic.
我在《国家地理》看到的
Mammal responses to rising temperatures and other climate changes...
哺乳动物提问会随外界环境改变而升高
Hi.
嗨
Is that your daughter?
那是你女儿吗
- Yeah, why? - Why? That's my son,
- 是的 怎么 - 那是我儿子
and they look like they're already best friends.
他们看上去好像已经成了好朋友
Yeah, Abby's probably telling him about the animals.
是啊 艾比可能正在和告诉他动物的事
Even as a baby, she was completely fascinated with them.
从很小的时候 她就迷上了那些动物
Yeah, he's the same. He likes extinct animals.
我儿子也是 他喜欢濒危物种
I'm John.
我叫约翰
Hi. Diana.
你好 迪安纳
What are they doing now?
现在他们在干嘛
Caleb's showing her something in sign language.
凯莱布在教她手语
- I'm sorry. I didn't realize... - He's not.
- 很抱歉 我不知道他… - 他不是
Sounds just get jumbled up sometimes.
有时事情并不是那么径渭分明
He has a hearing aid, which helps, but he's not deaf.
他带着助听器 但他不是聋子
He is an expert in sign language.
他在手语方面是专家
I don't think it's ever been this hot in October.
10月份不该这么热吧
Air conditioner must be out.
空调肯定出问题了
Dad, can we get a drink?
爸爸 我们能去喝点东西吗
Can we get one, too?
我们也能去喝点什么吗
Hey, would you and Abby like to join us?
不如我们一起吧
Sure, that'd be nice.
好啊
Abby, this is John.
艾比 这是约翰
- Hi. - Hey, Abby.
你好 艾比
What's that over there?
那边是什么
It can be tough sometimes, because, you know, I'm by myself.
有时候很难 因为我只有靠我自己
I know how you feel.
我能理解你的感受
- You're a single parent, too? - Yeah.
- 你也是单亲父母吗 - 是的
I kicked him out years ago.
几年前我甩了他
He couldn't keep his hands to himself,
他管不好他自己
so I decided he couldn't keep me to himself either.
所有我决定远离他
Well, it's... It's his loss.
这是他的损失
And you? You're separated, or...
那你呢 分居了还是…
Diana,
迪安纳
we didn't meet here by accident.
我们在这不是巧遇
I need to talk to you about something,
我需要和你谈些事情
ask you something about your mother.
一些关于你母亲的事
My mother? What about my mother?
我母亲的什么
Did she have some kind of ability?
她是不是有某种特异功能
Ability?
特异功能
A gift of some kind?
某种天赋
- Who are you? - Yeah, it's awkward. You don't know me.
- 你到底是谁 - 我知道 这很唐突 你还不认识我
I'm John Koestler. I teach astrophysics at MIT.
我是约翰·凯斯特勒 我在麻省理工学院教天体物理学
My son goes to William Dawes Elementary,
我儿子在威廉·道斯小学上学
which is the same school your mother went to.
也就是你母亲的母校
Fifty years ago, she put this in a time capsule. it's a list of dates,
50年前 她把这个放进了时光胶囊 这里面记录着
events that I think she believed would happen.
她认为将会发生的事件 日期
Look, I don't know what any of this is about...
听着 我完全不知道这些东西…
And I thought if I could talk to you or your father...
我想能和你谈一下或是你的父亲…
My father's dead.
我父亲也死了
I think it's possible that there are people, like your mother, Lucinda,
我认为有些人就像你的母亲卢辛达一样
who can see things before they occur.
他们可以预知未来
Abby, we're leaving!
艾比 我们走了
Honey?
宝贝
I followed one of your mother's predictions
我追踪你母亲的其中一个预言
and I watched 81 people burn to death in that plane crash yesterday,
昨天我目睹了飞机失事的81个人被活活烧死
when she said it would happen, where she said it would happen,
就在她预知的时间地点
and there was nothing I could do about it.
而我无能为力
She says 170 people will die tomorrow in New York City,
她预言明天纽约明天有170个人会死去
and in three days' time, October 19th, 33 more.
在三天时间里 10月19日 33个人
Stay away from me and my daughter.
离我和我女儿远点
Abby? Let's go, honey. Come on.
艾比 我们走了 快点
Stay right there. Diana?
别走 迪安纳
Diana, I think this has something to do with my son.
迪安纳 我觉得这跟我儿子有关
Get in there, honey.
上车亲爱的
I don't know how, or why, but I think he's in danger.
我不知道原因 但我觉得他深处险境
So I'm asking you please, please help us.
所以我请求你 求你帮助我们
I can't.
我办不到
A class-action suit brought by the families of the victims
死者家属正提出集体诉讼
is meant to be heard beginning next month.
这意味着下个月就要将开庭
Commuters along the Eastern Seaboard are reassessing their travel plans
东部沿海地区的人正重新考虑他们的旅行计划
in response to an FBI warning of a possible terrorist plot.
回应FBI的警告
The Department of Homeland Security raised the national threat level
国土安全部在听取情报机关的报告后
from elevated to high after intelligence reports suggested
把国家安全威胁级别又上升一个级别
an attack on a major East Coast city may be imminent.
东海岸一主要城市遭受袭击
Police have urged citizens to stay vigilant.
警方呼吁市民保持警觉
(拉斐特和沃思大街街口)
FBI New York, how may I direct your call?
FBI纽约分局 你要接哪个部门
The attack will take place tomorrow at the corner of Lafayette and Worth Streets.
明天会有一场袭击 在拉斐特和沃思大街转角
Cordon off the area from midnight. Are you clear on that?
从半夜开始警戒隔离那块地方 你听清楚了吗
Sir, let me patch you through to our agents...
先生 我帮您转接我们的探员
Please! Do exactly as I say or many people will die.
请照我说的做 否则会死很多人
This is not a crank call.
这可不是骚扰电话
You said you'd take him off my hands.
你说你可以代我照顾他
I know there's something you're not telling me.
我知道有些事你没告诉我
Don't let him watch the news.
不要让他看新闻
Well, traffic on the FDR right now is looking pretty heavy,
现在FDR上的交通异常拥堵
this gridlock we're looking at probably won't let up for hours.
几小时内是不会缓解了
Most of this traffic is headed downtown to the Westside...
大多数是开往西部城镇的
(沃思街)
(拉斐特街)
Why hasn't this intersection been sealed off?
这个路口为什么没有被封锁
Excuse me?
你说什么
I said why hasn't this intersection been sealed off?
我说这个路口为什么还没有封锁
- Didn't you get the tip-off about the attack? - Sir. Sir, please calm down.
- 你难道没接到关于袭击的通知吗 - 先生 先生 请冷静
If you'll accompany me, we'll get this matter taken care of.
如果你能随我来 我们可以处理这件事
Sir, stop!
先生 停下
- Hey, man. - Stop!
- 嘿 - 停下
I got him. Let's go! Move! Move!
我看到他了 走 走
Suspect sighted. Platform three.
发现可疑人物 三号站台
Hey!
嘿
Out of the way! Let me through!
让开 让我过去
Forward car.
进了列车
- Get off the train. - Why? What's wrong?
- 下车去 - 为什么 出什么事了
Just take the baby and get off the train.
带上你的孩子 下车
What's your problem, pal?
你有什么毛病 伙计
Hold it right there, sir.
站在那别动 先生
Transit police. I'm asking you to stop!
我是乘警 我命令你停下
That's him! You have to stop him!
是他 你应该阻止他
Transit police. Turn around.
乘警 转过身来
Now!
快点
Put your hands up!
把手举起来
Please! Please, I won't do it again, I promise! I'll give them back!
别开枪 别开枪 我再犯了 我保证 我会把这些都还回去的
I'll give them back! I'll give them back.
我把这些都还回去 都还回去
Next stop, Spring.
下一站 春天站
Move back! Move back!
后退 后退
Get out of the way!
让开
Move outside.
往外走
...make their way through the massive tangle of wreckage...
搜救人员穿过地铁残骸
...New York City subway disaster since...
1920年以来 纽约最严重的地铁灾难
It could be the result of a terrorist plot...
这可能是恐怖袭击造成的
Federal Aviation Administration officials
联邦航空管理局官员
are investigating a possible link to the electrostatic bursts
正在调查两天前失事的飞机
believed to have caused the Lexington air disaster of two days ago.
是否与静电脉冲有关
And NOAA, the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration,
国家大气海洋管理局
remains silent tonight.
今晚仍然保持沉默
But with the devastating subway crash in Manhattan,
但是随着曼哈顿地铁难的发生
power cuts in Long Island and two more emergency...
出现停电和其他紧急情况
Grace. I got held up by work. I'll be over in 30 minutes.
格莱斯 我一直在忙工作 再有半小时就搞定了
No, I'm fine. I'll see you in 30 minutes.
没事 我很好 半小时后见
- Three, four, five... - Five, six...
- 三 四 五 - 五 六
Caleb, go inside.
凯莱布 进屋去
- Hey. - Hi.
- 嘿 - 嗨
- Want to check out the house? - Sure.
- 想到屋子里看看吗 - 当然
You said October 19th?
你说到了10月19号
My mother used to talk about that day all the time.
我妈妈过去一直在说那天
She said it was the day I was going to die.
她说那天我会死
All my life I've had this thing hanging over my head
我这一生都生活在这事的阴影下
and Abby's.
艾比也是
I just don't believe anyone can predict my future.
我只是不相信有人能预言我的未来
And what does it matter, anyway?
可话说回来 那又怎样
We all die in the end.
我们最终都难逃一死
I don't want to know what my future holds.
我只是不想知道我的未来是怎样的
Last year, my wife was on a business trip to Phoenix
去年 我妻子出差去凤凰城
a few days before my birthday
就在我生日的前几天
and a fire started in her hotel at 4:00 in the morning.
凌晨四点 她住的旅馆着了大火
The investigators said that Allison died of smoke inhalation.
调查员说艾利森死于烟中毒
Died in her sleep.
当时她还睡着
She wouldn't have known anything about it.
根本什么也不知道
While she was dying, I was at home, in the front yard.
那个时候我在家里的前院
I always thought you were supposed to sense
以前我总以为当你所爱的人
when the people you love are in danger,
遇到危险时你会有所感觉
but I didn't feel anything.
但我却什么也没感觉到
Nothing.
什么也没有
I was just blowing leaves off the lawn.
我就在那清扫草坪上的落叶
I'm so sorry, John.
很抱歉 约翰
Well, but my point is that from then on,
从那时起 我的观点发生了改变
I decided that no one can know what was coming,
我相信没有人可以知道会发生什么事
and life was just a string of random accidents and mistakes.
人生只是一连串随机的巧合和意外
And then I got that list.
然后我得到了那张纸
If that had come to me before Allison left, I would have saved her life.
如果我在艾利森离开之前就得到那张表 我就能救她的命
I need to know.
我得知道
It's still here.
还在这
What's this?
这是什么
Have you seen this?
你看到这个了吗
Abby used to do this sometimes, write things backwards,
有的时候艾比也会把字反过来写
and that last number, I don't think it's 33.
最后两个数字 我不认为是33
It's EE.
是EE
EE? Initials. Someone she knew?
EE 首字母 是她认识的人吗
I don't know.
我不知道
I was nine when she overdosed.
我九岁那年 她就开始大量服药
The only time I ever came out here was with my father
我只来过这一次 和我爸爸一起
when he identified her body.
他是来辨认尸体的
She willed the property to me,
她把遗产留给了我
but I never came back for any of her things.
但我从没有回来取过任何东西
When I was little, my mother used to tell me that she could hear voices
在我还小的时候 妈妈告诉我说她能听见
whispering to her,
有人和她低语
telling her horrible things.
告诉她可怕的事情
And then one day, my dad came and took me away from her.
然后有一天 我爸爸来把我从她身边接走了
He said she was sick.
他说她病了
She said she moved out here to get ready.
她说她要搬走 去做好准备
I never knew what she meant by that.
我不知道那是什么意思
I made this for her one Christmas.
有一年圣诞节 我给她做了这个
I never knew she kept it.
我都不知道她保留着这个
(灾难…9000人死亡)
(南极洲257人死亡)
(洪水夺走113条人命)
(大火造成134人死亡)
(英国的油轮悲剧)
(1978年的暴风雪)
(东德矿坑崩塌238人死亡)
(以西结书第1章)
She used to stare at this picture for hours.
她常常盯着这幅画 一看就是几个小时
That's where they found her.
我们就是在那找到的她
In there.
在那
(圣经)
Have you seen enough?
你看够了吗
Yeah. Okay. We'll go.
好了 可以了 我们走
Abby?
艾比
Abby.
Caleb.
凯莱布
Come.
来吧
Come with us.
跟我来
EE isn't just one person.
EE代表的不仅仅是一个人
(所有人…无一幸免)
Abby, no!
艾比不要
Abby!
艾比
What? What? What? It's okay. It's okay.
怎么了 怎么了 好了 没事了
They were here.
他们来了
Who? Who was here, Caleb?
谁 谁来了 凯莱布
- Did they hurt you? - No. They were talking to us.
- 他们伤到你们了吗 - 没 他们在和我们谈话
- What did they say? - I don't know. They were all talking at once.
- 他们说什么 - 我不知道 他们同时在说话
They said we could go with them, if we chose to.
他们说如果我们愿意 可以和他们走
- Who did, baby? Who? - The whisper people.
- 谁说的 宝贝 谁 - 耳语者
Hey, lock the doors.
把门锁上
What do you want with my son?
你想对我儿子怎样
Answer me!
回答我
I just know they've been following us for days.
我只知道他们跟着我们许多天了
I think someone's been following me and Abby, too.
我也觉得有人在跟着我和艾比
That's why she didn't write any coordinates down after the final date.
这就为什么她没有在 日期后面写出地点的原因
There isn't a single location this time.
这次根本就不是一个地点
Are you telling me that my mother could see the end of everything?
你是想告诉我说 我妈妈可以预言世界末日
That we're all going to die tomorrow?
我们明天都会死
She was disturbed, John. She could've just made it all up.
她疯了 约翰 这可能是她编的
She's been right so far, Diana.
到目前为止 她的预言都是准确的 迪安纳
About everything.
所有的预言都实现了
Abby's... Abby's all I've got, John.
艾比 艾比是我的一切 约翰
I can't let anything happen to her.
我不能让她有任何闪失
Caleb, you really need to sleep.
凯莱布 你真的要睡觉了
I can hear them whispering to me sometimes like Abby can.
有时候我也像艾比一样 能听到他们对我低语
Could Lucinda hear them, too?
是不是卢辛达也能听见
Yeah, I think she did. Yes.
是的 我认为她也能听见
Are me and Abby gonna die?
我和艾比是不是会死
No. I will never let that happen, Caleb.
不会 我不会让你们有事的 凯莱布
Do you hear me? Never.
听见了吗 永远不会
You...
你
(和我…)
(永远在一起)
Abby, what do you like to eat for breakfast?
艾比 早饭想吃点什么
Ab by?
艾比
What are you doing, honey?
你干什么呢 宝贝
It's the sun.
是太阳
There's something I need to check. Get Abby, you're coming with us.
有件事我的确认一下 带上艾比和我们来
Caleb!
凯莱布
Okay. All right.
好的 好了
Hey, John, what happened?
约翰 出什么事了
Hey!
嘿
Talk to me. What happened?
告诉我 出什么事了
I've been calling you off the hook ever since I heard about the subway.
自从我听说地铁难之后 我就一直在给你打电话
John?
约翰
Do you remember that paper on extra-solar activity I published?
还记得我发表的那篇关于 太阳外部活动的论文吗
Yeah, sure, I remember.
当然记得
I found evidence of a series of super-flares
我在外太空区域发现了
from a star in the outer-Pleiades region.
恒星发出超级耀斑的迹象
Right. Ratings were off the chart.
是啊 等级超出了记录范围
We were both wrong. The numbers are a warning,
我们都错了 这些数字只是警告
but not just to me or any random group.
不仅仅是对我 或者什么组织
They're a warning to everyone.
是对全人类的警告
Okay. You're officially scaring the shit out of me right now.
好了 你那么正经的样子吓到我了
The super-flare, in our own solar system.
超级耀斑 在我们自己的太阳系中
A 100 microtesla wave of radiation
100微特斯拉的微波辐射
that would destroy our ozone layer, killing every living organism on the planet.
将会破坏臭氧层 杀死地球上所有的生物
We have to let everyone know. We have to call the NOAA.
我们必须通知大家 我们得告诉海洋大气局
They already know. The announcement will come anytime now.
他们已经知道了 他们可能会在任何时刻发出公告
I thought there was some purpose to all of this.
我就觉得这一切不是巧合
Why did I get this prediction if there's nothing I can do about it?
如果我无能为力 那为什么是我得到预言
How am I supposed to stop the end of the world?
我怎么才能阻止世界末日
Go home, Phil. Be with Kim tonight.
回家去吧 菲尔 回去陪着金姆吧
Diana.
迪安纳
I'm so stupid.
我真是太愚蠢了
I've spent my whole life knowing she was right
我这一辈子一直都知道她是对的
and pretending that she was insane.
却假装她是个疯子
If we hide underground, we've got a chance, don't we?
如果我们藏到地下 我们还有机会吗 是吗
It's possible.
也许吧
I know some caves off Route 40 past Groton.
我知道在格罗顿40号公路附近有些洞
Hardly anyone knows about them, but I used to play there as a child.
我小时候经常在那玩 几乎没人知道那里
We could try there, right?
我们可以去那试试 是吗
- Okay - Okay
- 好吧 - 好的
Caleb, put some clothes and shoes into your backpack.
凯莱布 装些衣服和鞋子到包里
Diana, load all the non-perishable food, any water you can, into the truck.
迪安纳 装上所有易保存的食品 以及所有 能装到车上的水
Let's try to be out of here in 10 minutes.
我们要在十分钟内离开这里
- You start. I'll get some bags. - Yeah.
- 你开始装 我找些袋子 - 好的
(永远在一起)
Allison wanted me to call you
艾利森出差去凤凰城那天
the day she left for Phoenix.
就曾让我给你打电话
She wanted me to promise her that I'd call you.
她让我保证一定打给你
I know, Jonathan.
我知道 约翰
We haven't spoken in so long, I don't really even know why anymore.
我们很久没说过话了 我都不知道是为什么
I need to tell you something.
有件事我得告诉你
Yes?
说吧
That sermon you preached every year at Pentecost, about the gifts of the Spirit,
每年圣灵降临节那天 你布道的 关于上帝礼物的说教
one was the gift of prophecy.
其中之一是预言的礼物
1 Corinthians 12-Yes, I remember it. The church should respect the prophet.
哥林多前书第12章 我记得 教会应该尊重先知
I have a prophecy.
我得到个预言
It's about to be proven accurate.
过不了多久就会实现
I need you to respect it and receive it as the truth.
我想让你认真考虑下 相信这是真的
This heat we're experiencing isn't going to get better.
地球上的温度可能会发生改变
It's going to get worse, much worse.
可能会变的很糟 非常糟
I need you to get Mom and Grace and any supplies you can,
你带上妈妈和格莱斯 和一切能带的补给品
and get below ground tonight. The basement, the sewer, the T.
躲到地下去今晚 地下室 下水道 防空洞
Just get as deep as you can and as fast as you can.
能躲多深就躲多深
And that will keep us safe from this heat?
那能让我们安全躲过热浪的袭击吗
I don't know that, but we have to try, right?
我不知道 但我们总得试试 不是吗
I'm sorry, John, but I'm afraid I'm not going anywhere tonight or any night.
对不起 约翰 我那也不去 不管是今晚还是其他晚上
I appreciate your concern, but if it's my time, it's my time.
谢谢你的关心 但如果我的时间到了 就让我去吧
I'm ready whenever the good Lord calls me.
我时刻等待着上帝的召唤
Are you?
你呢
- Dad? - Hello?
- 爸爸 - 喂
- John? - Dad?
- 约翰 - 爸爸
(无讯号)
Caleb, let's go!
凯莱布 我们走了
Caleb.
凯莱布
Caleb!
Caleb, stop!
凯莱布 别写了
- Caleb! - Huh? Huh?
凯莱布
What were you doing?
你在干吗
Did I do that?
那是我弄的吗
This isn't the way to the highway.
这不是往公路的方向
(小学)
Everybody wait here.
都在这等着
John!
约翰
(体育馆)
John, please, why are we back here?
约翰 我们为什么回到这儿
John, please, what are you doing? We have to get to the caves.
约翰 你在干吗 我们得去山洞
- We're not going to the caves. - What?
- 我们不去山洞 - 什么
She knew the coordinates for this last event.
她知道最后这件事发生的座标
She tried to write them down.
她试着写下来
The teacher said she was interrupted, ran out of time,
老师说 她被打断了 因为时间到了
so she scratched them into this door.
所以她就用手刻到这扇门上了
She tried to tell us where to go.
她要告诉我们 该去哪
You're not making any sense. Look at you. Look at what you're doing!
你在说什么 看看你 看看你在干什么
The numbers are the key to everything.
那些数字是一切的关键
Please! Please, John, we need to leave!
求你了 求你了 约翰 我们得走了
We're taking my car. Come on. Let's go. Keep your bags with you.
坐我的车 快 我们走 把包带上
Be here, please, be here.
一定在这儿 拜托 一定要在这儿
Throw it in the back.
把东西丢后面
What about Dad?
我爸爸怎么办
He's just gotta finish what he's doing. He's gonna follow us.
他还有事 完成后会来找我们
We're just getting a head start, okay?
我们先走
Diana?
迪安纳
Caleb!
凯莱布
(无讯号)
Where are we going, Mom? Are we hiding from the whisper people?
妈妈 我们去哪 是要躲开说耳语者吗
Yes, baby. They won't find us where we're going.
是的 孩子 去他们找不到的地方
Mom, they know where we are.
妈妈 他们知道我们在哪
- How do you know that? - They told us so.
- 你怎么知道 - 他们说的
- You've seen them again? - No. They just talk to us.
- 你又看到他们了 - 没有 他们只和我们说话
How, Abby? How do they talk to you?
怎么说 艾比 他们怎么和你们说话
They whisper into our heads.
他们在我们的耳边说
Oh, God.
天
- I want to call my dad. - The phones are down!
- 我要打电话给我爸 - 电话接不通
I promise he's right behind us! We'll call him when we get there!
我保证 他就跟着我们 我们到了 就给他电话
Wait right here!
在车上待着
Now let's get back to the financial markets, if we may, for a moment.
现在让我们暂时回到金融市场
Let's check it out on the grid here this morning. We've got Treasuries moving up...
让我们今天上午检查一下系统 我们发现国债正在上涨
Yeah, thanks. Thanks, man.
是的 谢谢 谢谢 老兄
Number five.
5号
India is a better bet than the US or Europe,
和美国 欧洲相比 印度是更适合投资
and that the dollar will continue its long slide...
美元将继续下滑
20.
This is an Emergency Broadcast Transmission.
这是紧急广播
This is not a test. This is an Emergency Broadcast Transmission.
这不是演习 这是紧急广播
- Today, NOAA has concluded... - Turn that up!
- 今天 诺阿卫星得出推断 - 开大声点
... the solar flares may last longer
太阳耀斑可能会比我们想得持续更久
and cause more damage to our infrastructure than we originally thought.
并对我们的基础设施造成更大破坏
We're recommending that people stay indoors until further notice.
我们建议民众在收到通知前 待在家里
Bring your pets inside. Stock up on extra water and, if possible,
把宠物也带进家里 储存备用水
seek out fortified underground shelter.
可能的话 躲在坚固的地下藏身处
- General, what time is it happening? - General, excuse me...
- 将军 这是什么时候发生的 - 将军 请问
The shelters we have are currently ovenwhelmed.
目前我们的庇护所不堪重负
The best advice we can offer the public is to seek your own.
公众最好自己寻找避难所
Sir!
长官
One more question about the warning.
还有一个关于警报的问题
We are assessing this information as it becomes available.
一收到消息
It was only recently confirmed.
我们就马上核实了
Where is the President?
总统在哪
The President and his staff
总统和他的工作人员
are currently being transported to a secure location.
目前正被转移到安全的地点
- Hello? - Dad?
- 喂 - 爸
Caleb, are you okay? Tell me exactly where you are.
凯莱布 你好吗 告诉我 你的具体位置
We're at a gas station. I don't know where.
我们在加油站 我不知道加油站在哪
The damage information regarding the destructive power of these flares
关于这些耀斑的破坏程度
is a scientific matter, and I'm not gonna speculate...
属于科学问题 我无法解释
Are you coming with us?
你和我们一起走吗
I need you to stay right there. Get me an...
我要你待在那别动 给我一…
Caleb, get back to the car now.
凯莱布 马上回到车上
- Caleb? - John?
- 凯莱布 - 约翰
- Where are you? - We're in Westford.
- 你们在哪 - 我们在威斯福特镇
I'm sorry. I had to do this for Abby and for Caleb.
对不起 为了艾比和凯莱布 我必须这么做
- I'm taking them to the caves. - I found the numbers!
- 我带他们去山洞 - 我找到数字了
They're the location of your mother's mobile home.
位置就在你母亲的活动房
That's where we've got to go.
那才是我们要去的地方
- Don't do this to me. Please. - I know how it sounds.
- 不要这样对我 求你了 - 我了解
You want us to head toward the place where this is supposed to happen?
你要我们去事件发生的地方吗
Are you insane?
你疯了吗
It's a chance we gotta take or we're all gonna die!
这是我们唯一的机会 否则我们都会死
Stay where you are! I'll be right there!
待在那 我马上到
No! If we go to the caves, we have a chance!
不行 如果去山洞 我们还有机会活下来
You said the sun can't reach that far!
你说过 太阳照不到那
The caves won't save us! Nothing can!
山洞救不了我们 没有什么能救我们
The radiation will penetrate a mile into the Earth's crust! Do you hear me?
辐射会渗透到 地壳下一英里的地方 听到了吗
Our only shot is to go where the numbers want us to go.
唯一的机会是去数字指引的地方
- It's what we're meant to do! - No, I don't believe you!
- 这才是我们该做的 - 不 我不相信你
I'm taking the children! We have to save the children!
我带孩子们去 我们要救孩子们
Don't you move, Diana! Caleb is my son, and I'll decide where he goes!
别走 迪安纳凯 莱布是我儿子 他去哪 我说了算
Diana! Caleb! Are you there?
迪安纳 凯莱布 你们还在吗
Abby!
艾比
Abby! Abby!
艾比 艾比
Help! Somebody took my daughter!
救命啊 有人抓了我女儿
Abby!
艾比
Damn it!
该死的
Where did she go?
她去哪了
Everyone needs to do this immediately.
每个人都需要立即这样做
We are facing a natural threat of global proportions,
我们正面临全球范围的自然威胁
and there is very little that this government...
而且政府能做的很少
Same thing happened with Y2K.
2000年也发生了同样的事
They are gonna wake up tomorrow morning feeling pretty stupid.
他们明天一觉醒来 就会觉得自己很愚蠢
Thirty minutes ago there was a woman here. She was screaming!
30分钟前有个女人在这儿 一直尖叫
She was with a kid! He was on your pay phone! He's a nine- year- old kid!
她带着个孩子 9岁大 他用了付费电话
Some guy took the lady's car with the kids inside. Drove right off with it.
有人开走了那女人的车 孩子们都在车上 呼地一下开跑了
- The woman, where'd she go? - That way!
- 那女人 往哪去了 - 那边
Go lock the door! Stop that, you crazy...
去锁门 放下 你这个疯子
You've got to pay for that! Hey, stop!
你还没付钱 喂 别跑
You need to seek protection from the sun
你们得找个晒不到太阳的地方 马上去找
and it needs to be immediately.
并且立即需要
We're facing a deadly threat.
我们正面临着一个致命的威胁
- Get out! - I didn't see you!
- 出来 - 我没看到你
Hey! Get out of here!
出来
- Is she... Where are the children? - We can't help you now, sir.
- 她… 孩子们在哪 - 先生 我们现在没法帮你
Calm down, all of you! Just calm down!
冷静 所有人 冷静
Charge.
充电
Clear.
离手
Again.
再来
Clear.
离手
- Okay, call it. - 12:00 midnight exactly.
- 宣布死亡 - 午夜12点整
There's a man down. We need help.
(10月19日)
有个男人受伤了 我们需要帮助
Diana.
迪安纳
I'm sorry.
对不起
Caleb!
凯莱布
Where is he?
他在哪
Where's Caleb?
凯莱布在哪
I want my son!
我要我的儿子
Now!
现在
Dad, don't!
爸爸 不要
Are you hurt? What did he do to you?
你受伤了吗 他对你做了什么
It's okay, Dad. I'm okay. This is my friend.
我很好 爸爸 我很好 这是我的朋友
They said I can keep him.
他们说我可以留着它
Caleb, I want you to come with me. We're going now.
凯莱布 跟我走 我们现在走
But we have to go with them.
但是我们得跟他们走
They won't hurt us.
他们不会伤害我们
Abby, are you okay?
艾比 你好吗
- Your mom wanted to be here, honey. - I know.
- 你妈妈想来的 宝贝 - 我知道
The whisper people told me that Mommy's safe now.
耳语者告诉我 妈妈现在很安全
They've been protecting us all along, Dad.
爸爸 他们一直在保护我们
They sent a message ahead of them to prepare the way,
他们之前就发出信息 让大家做好准备
and now they've come for us.
现在他们来接我们了
Who are you?
你们是什么人
It's time to go, Dad. They've chosen us so we can start over.
爸爸 该走了 他们选了我们 我们可以重新开始了
So everything can start over.
一切都可以重新开始
What do you mean? I don't understand.
什么意思 我不明白
Why is he saying that, Dad?
他为什么这么说 爸爸
What?
什么
What's he saying, Caleb?
他说什么了 凯莱布
He's saying only the chosen must go,
他说 只有被选上的人才能去
those who heard the call.
那些听到召唤的人
Please.
求你了
I can't go with you, Caleb. I mean, I can't go with you.
凯莱布 我不能和你一起去了 我不能和你一起去了
They've chosen us to go.
他们选我们去了
They haven't chosen us, Caleb.
他们没有选择我们 凯莱布
They've chosen you, both of you.
他们选择了你们 你们两个
You have to take care of Abby now. You have to be strong for her.
现在你要照顾艾比 为了她 你要坚强
No. I don't want to go without you.
不 我不要离开你
They could've taken you away from me, but they didn't,
他们本来可以直接带你走 但他们没有
because you have to make this decision yourself.
因为你要自己决定
But you promised.
但你答应过
You said we'd be together forever.
你说 我们会永远在一起
We will be. We will be. I'm not leaving you.
我们会的 我们会的 我不会离开你
But you gotta go with them. You gotta go. You gotta go with them.
但你得跟他们走 你得去 你得跟他们去
Caleb, Caleb, listen to me, Caleb. Stop, stop.
凯莱布 凯莱布 听我说 凯莱布 别哭了 别哭了
Stop. Listen to me. Listen.
别哭了 听我说 听
We're gonna be together. We're all gonna be together.
我们会在一起的 我们会在一起
And Mom's gonna be with us, too.
妈妈也会和我们在一起的
I know it. I know that now. I know it.
我知道 我现在知道了 我知道了
Look. Here. Take this.
带上这个
Take this. Keep it with you.
带着 随身戴着
One day, you'll know what it means.
终有一天 你会知道这意味着什么
I love you, Daddy.
我爱你 爸爸
(你和我…)
(永远在一起)
Where's Caleb?
凯莱布在哪里
Caleb's safe.
凯莱布很安全
We're going to stay on the air for as long as possible.
(全球危机)
我们会尽可能一直直播
All we can say is what we've been repeating all morning.
我们所能说的是 整个上午一直在重复的
Get to any kind of underground shelter.
躲进任何类型的地下避难所
We've been told the satellite...
我们刚得知 卫星…
This isn't the end, Son.
这不是世界末日 儿子
I know.
我知道
-=旧域名被黑 启用新网址=-
-=梦幻天堂·龙网=-
http://www.lwgod.com